

NGUYEN NU MY MY

Senior Sourcing & Merchandiser/ Modern Trade Manager

Date of birth: June 6, 1989

Gender: Female

Phone: 0988388121

Email: nguyennumymy@gmail.com

Binh Chanh, HCMC Address:

OBJECTIVES

With the extensive experience on a wide variety of areas including sourcing, merchandising, sales planning, commercial management with strong local market and product understanding, I aim to become an expert in sourcing and merchandising, adding more values to the company and help facilitate the process of product distribution to consumers, thereby helping the company to improve the customer base and sales as well as enable market expansion and market development.

EDUCATION

September 2007 - May 2013

HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

Bachelor of Food Technology

GPA: 3/4

October 2015 - November 2017 UNIVER OF FINANCE- MARKETING

Master of degree

GPA: 3/4

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nov 2023 - Present

MTV GLOBAL MALL COMPANY

Now 2023 -> 2024 - Build over 500 products sold on e-commerce platform

FREELANCER

Manage: 30 Suppliers & 15 Staffs (Official employees and interns)

Report: CEO

- Build company booths on e-commerce platforms: shopee, lazada, tiktok
- Build a dropship model between suppliers and e-commerce platforms
- Development products
- Identifying potential suppliers and evaluating their capabilities.
- Negotiate & purchase: managed purchasing contracts for foods, supplement foods, cosmetics, health care
- Developing plans to promote sales
- Responsible for conducting strategic plans.
- Recruiting, training, settling rights for staffs

Nov 2018 - Nov 2023

VI VI TRADING JOINT STOCK COMPANY

(VGSSHOP, GS SHOP, SONKIM RETAIL) - Biggest Homeshopping in Vietnam 1(1,000 stores - 2017 turnover of \$400M)

Merchandiser Manager of Foods & Health Food

Manage: 30 Suppliers & 31 Staffs (30 call center & 01 admin)

Report: CEO

- o Identifying potential suppliers and evaluating their capabilities.
- Negotiate & purchase: ensured profitability, built proactive purchase plans with seasonal suppliers, longterm partners and managed purchasing contracts for foods (drinks, candy, dried fruits, noodles,milks...), supplement foods (function foods, health care..)
- Collection implementation: built collections (every 3 months), forecasted demands, developed collections with suppliers
- Promotion campaign execution (every 3 weeks): defined the catalogue products list and dealt with suppliers
- Data analysis: followed up sales figures and controlledaction plans
- o Collaborating with various internal departments to contact purchase orders.
- Inventory Management analyzing demand, purchase and process component inventory.
- Supplier Management managing current to ensure that orders are delivered by the committed date
- Cost and Quality Management enabling access to favorable pricing and conditions whilst maintaining a high standard of quality

Aug 2017 - Oct 2018

LAMY SERVICE TRADING COMPANY

Sales Manager

- Running and managing offers, orders, sales promotion and delivery process at the point of sale.
- Development products
- Developing plans to promote sales.

Step 2016 - Jan 2017

THAI SON LTD S.P

Consultant specialist

Advisory support on products sold on the company channels for Thai Son Home shopping S.P

- Responsible for conducting strategic plans.
- Training personnel
- Developing products
- Analyzing buyer behavior
- Developing content for product screenplay and the main focus of the script
- Creating new contracts with customers such as SCJ, VGS, SAONAM
- Developing plans to promote sales of supermarkets at the end of 2016. For example, the program "Sharing love with Aloha and Vietclio" at 25 Coopmart branches.

Aug 2012 - Sep 2016

ESC CORPORATION VIETNAM

Sales Manager MT

From 8/2012 to 12/2013

- In charge of monthly management, consultancy and PG supermarket's sales
- Running sales events for supermarket channels in the MT system (e.g. Coopmart, Vinatex, Lotte, TTDM Thien Hoa, Phan Khang TTDM)
- Recruiting, training, settling rights for PG

From May 1/2014 -> 12/2014

- Managing the company's customer such as Vinatextmart MT, TTDM 30/4, Giant.
- Running and managing offers, orders, sales promotion and delivery process at the point of sales

From January / 2015-> 07/2015

- In charge of sourcing new customers from online channels such as SCJ, Lotte Land Vietnam Homshopping, VGS, Lazada, Tiki.....
- +Conducting and executing marketing plans in line with set strategic plan

From August / 2015-> 12/2016

- Charging supermarket channel management, electronics center and online channels across the country's brand Honey's.
- Developing sales plans, expanding market and market share
- Recruiting and managing PG of the system to grow sales.

Jan 2011 - Aug 2012

BRAND CAKE GOCHEESE, AUSTRALIAN WINE

Sale staff

- Product consulting at Australian wine brand, Hokera and other channels such as restaurants, hotels in central districts as Q1, Q3, Q5
- o Sourcing new customers
- Managing wholesale clients of Gocheese across HCM city.

Dec 2007 - Oct 2010

ADVERTISING COMPANIES

PG

Working while studying

JW wine marketing

Marketing local tobacco brands (e.g, 555, Pall Mall, CarventA,

PG events

CERTIFICATIONS

2011 Certificate of Business Administration (with honors)

HONORS & AWARDS

2013	Excellent Employee of the year
2015	Excellent Sales Supervisor of the first 6 months of the year
2015	Excellent Sales Supervisor of the year

SKILLS

Language	Vietnamese
Computer	Word, Excel, PowerPoint

INTERESTS

Research, books, music.

REFERENCES

- o Nguyen Bac Son. Business manager. Phone number: 0903 984 246 Thai Son Co. S.P.
- Nguyen Van Truong. Retail Chain Manager. Phone number: 0902527799. JSC ESC
 Vietnam
- Chau Hoang. Deputy Director GS SHOP. Phone number: 098 334 3304. VI VI COMPANY
- Nguyen Van Thu. CEO. Phone number: 0989 442 724 MTV GLOBAL MALL COMPANY